# **Christyasto Priyonggo Pambudi**

Jakarta, Indonesia | https://bit.ly/christyastoCV WhatsApp. +6281315681547 | christyasto.chito@gmail.com

# **ABOUT**

A Research Officer with 3+ years of experience in the field of Architecture and Software Development. Adept in the usage of Computer-Aided Design Software and Microsoft Office products. Inquisitive by nature, ever excited to learn new things and always looking for opportunities to expand his horizon!



#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **SUTD International Design Centre**

(April 2019 - June 2020)

Research Officer

- Led in the investigation of new biomaterial potential as a building material.
- Co-author of the research paper produced.
- Managed overseas lab production scheduling and planning.
- Designed and conducted prototyping & digital fabrications.
- Adopted learning of new skills required for biomaterial analysis methods.
- Developed a plugin for pixel analysis of biomaterial sample (Grasshopper).

SUTD SURGe Lab (March 2018 - March 2019)

Research Officer

- Front-end design and development for responsive multi-platform web-app (HTML, EJS).
- Set up booth to promote app for user testing.
- Research materials procurement.

# AA Visiting School Bamboo Lab – Myanmar & Indonesia

(November 2018 & November 2019)

**Assistant Tutor** 

- Introduced students to CAD software (Rhinoceros 3D) and parametric design.
- Assisted the Bamboo-based Architectural Design studio.

# **SUTD Advanced Architecture Lab**

(May 2015 - September 2017)

Student Researcher

- UI Development on a Grasshopper optimization component written in C#.
- Developed a benchmarking plugin to log software performance.
- Digital fabrication & manufacturing of parts for several architectural projects.
- Architectural model making.

# W Singapore - Sentosa Cove

(February 2014 - May 2014)

Part-time Waiter

Waiter for hotel restaurant and banquets.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### SINGAPORE UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY AND DESIGN

Architecture and Sustainable Development – B.Sc. (Architecture)

May 2014 - September 2017 3.36/5.00 - Cum Laude

- Executive Committee of Taekwondo Club for 2 years.
- Member of SUTD choir.

# **OTHER EXPERIENCES**

- Young Adults' Fellowship Committee in Gethsemane Bible-Presbyterian Church Singapore.
- Member of church choir.

# **SKILLS**

- Competent in 3D Computer-Aided Design software such as Rhinoceros, Grasshopper, AutoCAD.
- Competent in Adobe Creative Cloud products Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Audition.
- Working experience with programming languages C#, C++, HTML, JavaScript, and EJS.
- Some learning exposures in Python, Java, VBA and MySQL.
- Competent in Microsoft Office Programs Word, PowerPoint, Excel.

# **LANGUAGE**

- Indonesia Native mother tongue.
- English Lived in Singapore for over 12 years since secondary school.
- Javanese Limited informal conversations.

# **COMPETITIONS**

Singapore Founder's Memorial Design Competition

March 2019

**TATA Customer Service Centre Design** 

March 2017

1<sup>st</sup> Place

**EVOLO 2017** 

January 2017

**ISTD Receptionist Design** 

September 2016

1<sup>st</sup> Runner-up

**International BIM Competition 2016** 

August 2016